Finding Aid for the Lou Hackett Silberman
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Lou Hackett Silberman Papers
1930s-1980
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0392
20.56 linear_feet
This collection contains the papers of Lou Hackett Silberman, longtime Hillel Professor of Jewish Literature and Thought at Vanderbilt University. Silberman also participated throughout his career in a variety of Hillel Foundation and other B'nai B'rith activities and was especially active in lecturing to various Jewish groups as well as in interreligious dialogue.
List of acronyms and their meaning:
AAR
AOL
AJC
AJS
ASSR
ATS
AZA
BBYO
BTI
CARA
CCAR
CJF
CJT
CSRE
CSTS
HUC
IJF
IRJT
ISCP
ITESS
JAAR
JWF
JUUU
MAC
NAJCC
NCC
NCRAC
NCRC
OEC
REA
RRC
SBL
SNTS
SORJ
SUNY
TCHR
UAHC
UTS
WCC-IJCIC
1914 Born June 23, 1914 to Lou Harry and Myrtle Mueller Silberman in San Francisco, California. The Silberman family lived in San Francisco and in Los Angeles, California.
1934 B.A., University of California, Berkeley in Philosophy.
1934-35 Graduate student in Philosophy at University of California, Berkeley.
1935-43 Student at Hebrew Union College, Cincinnati, Ohio. Silberman received the B.Heb.L. (1939), M.Heb.L. (1941), D.Heb.L. (1943). His doctoral work was on medieval Jewish apologetics and polemics. While at H.U.C., Silberman studied under the noted Jewish scholars Jacob Z. Lauterbach, Samuel S. Cohon, and Julian Morgenstern.
1941-43 Fellow and Instructor in Medieval Exegesis, Hebrew Union College.
1941 Ordained a Rabbi.
1942 Married Helen Epstein on June 14, 1942. The Silbermans had two daughters, Syrl Augusta and Deborah Sue.
1943-45 Assistant Rabbi, Temple Emanu-el, Dallas Texas.
1945-52 Rabbi, Temple Israel, Omaha, Nebraska. Throughout his rabbinic and academic career, Silberman was involved in the affairs and institutions of Reform Judaism and he served the Central Conference of American Rabbis in a variety of capacities.
1952-55 Associate Professor of Jewish Literature and Thought, Vanderbilt University. Silberman replaced Samuel Sandmel in a chair partially funded through the auspices of the Hillel Foundation of B’ nai B’ rith. Silberman also participated throughout his career in a variety of Hillel Foundation and other B’ nai B’ rith activities and was especially active in lecturing to various Jewish Groups as well as in interreligious dialogue.
1955-80 Hillel Professor of Jewish Literature and Thought, Vanderbilt University.
1959 Sabbatical at the University of Basel.
1959-60 President, Society of Biblical Literature (Southern Section).
1960 James Lawson expelled from Vanderbilt Divinity School for his Civil Rights activities. Silberman was a leader in the faculty efforts to restore Lawson and he was one of the faculty members to submit resignations when the efforts of the faculty failed. His social justice activities extended to the community as well where he served on the Metro Action Commission of Nashville and the Tennessee Council on Human Relations. In addition, he served for a time as Vice-Chair, National Community Relations Advisory Council.
1960-61 Acting Chair, Graduate Department of Religion, Vanderbilt University.
1960-65 Director of Graduate Studies in the Biblical Area, Graduate 1967-68 Department of Religion, Vanderbilt University.
1965-66 Sabbatical, Visiting Professor, Judiastik Institut, University of Vienna.
1972 Visiting Professor, Carleton College (Winter).
1973 Visiting Professor, John Carroll University (Winter); Emory University (Spring).
1978 Sabbatical, Visiting Professor, University of Chicago Divinity School (Winter-Spring); Visiting Scholar, Oxford Centre for Postgraduate Hebrew Studies (Summer).
1979 Recipient, Thomas Jefferson Award, Vanderbilt University.
1979 Death of wife, Helen Epstein Silberman, in late October.
1980 Hillel Professor of Jewish Literature and Thought, Emeritus, Vanderbilt University.
1980 Fellow, Toronto School of Theology.
1981 Visiting Professor, Department of Oriental Languages, University of Arizona.
1982 President, Society of Biblical Literature. Silberman was actively involved throughout his career in a number of scholarly societies including the Society of Biblical Literature, the American Academy of Religion, the American Society for the Study of Religion, the American Theological Society, the Association for Jewish Studies, and Studiorum Novi Testamenti Societas. In addition, he served on the Advisory Council on Theological Education of the Danforth Foundation.
- Correspondence
  - Outgoing, April 13, 1945 - Dec. 6, 1963 (Box 1)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 14, 1964 - May 29, 1970 (Box 2)
  - Outgoing, June 1, 1970 - March 1975 (Box 3)
  - Outgoing, April 2, 1975 - June 2, 1980, undated (Box 4)
  - Incoming, Aaronsohn - Broun, D. (Box 5)
  - Incoming, Brown, 6. - Evans (Box 6)
  - Incoming, Facher - Grant (Box 7)
  - Incoming, Graubert - Jacobs (Box 8)
  - Incoming, Jacobson - Kushner (Box 9)
  - Incoming, Lagemann - Moran (Box 10)
  - Incoming, Morgan - Purdy (Box 11)
  - Incoming, Robinowitz - Siegel (Box 12)
  - Incoming, Siegman - Waldauer (Box 13)
  - Incoming, Walden - Zussman, Unidentified (Box 14)
- Writings and Speeches by Silberman
  - Articles
    - Anent the Use of Rabbinic Materials (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Apocalyptic Revisited (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Between Chaos and Creation (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Between God and Man (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Between God and Man (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Class Differences - Concerning Jewish Theology: Some After-Thoughts (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Concerning Jewish Theology in North America: Some Notes on a Decade (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Death in the Hebrew Bible (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Ezrabucher (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Farewell to Confirmation (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Farewell to o amhn - From Civil Rights to Human Rights (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - God and Man (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - God and Man (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - God and Man (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - "Habent Sua Fata...":The Role of Wandering Themes (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - The Human Deed in a Time of Despair (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - The Interreligious Situation: A Not Entirely Bleak View (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - The Jewish Image of God - Jubilees (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Judaism (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Judaism (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Lag Beomer (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Language and Structure in the Hodayot (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Language and Structure in the Hodayot (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - The Making of the Old Testament Canon (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Manus Uelatae - Mediation (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - A Midrash on Midrash - Original Sin (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - The Paradoxes of Freedom and Authority (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Precis - Prolegomenon (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Prophets and Angels (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Queen of Sheba (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Religion and the Freedom of the Artist (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Religious Education and Style - Reprobation, Prohibition and Invalidity (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Revelation in Judaism (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - The Search for Relevance (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Sitra Ahra (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Social Ethics and/or Social Action (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - The State of the Reform Movement (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - The Theologian'5 Task (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Theology and Philosophy (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Theology and Philosophy (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Theology and Philosophy (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Theology and Philosophy (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Toward a Rhetoric of Midrash (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Toward a Rheotric of Midrash (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - The Transmigration of a Tale (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - The Union Prayer Book (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - The University and Jewish Studies (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Unriddling the Riddle (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Unriddling the Riddle (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Wellhausen and Judaism (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Whence Siglum Q? A Conjecture (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous Encyclopedia Articles (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Unidentified Notes - Unidentified Articles (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Citadel of Books (2nd draft) (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Citadel of Books (Partial Oraft) (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Manuscripts, Lectures, and Speeches
    - Book Manuscript: Citadel of Books, Partial Draft (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Book Manuscript: Citadel of Books, Partial Draft (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Book Manuscript: Our Tradition, Partial Draft (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Book Manuscript: Our Tradition, Partial Drafts (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Book Manuscript: American Impact (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Speech re: American Jewish Community (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - The American Jewish Community and its Values (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - B'nai B'rith Yough Organization Talks (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Commencement Address; Educational Policy Committee Presentation (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - For Theodore H. Gaster; Form and Faith (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - The Future of Reform Judaism (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Talk re: Graduate Education; Tribute to Ualter Harrelson (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Hillel Directors Conference Address (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Holocaust Lectures Introductions (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - The Holy Community - An Anguished Appraisal (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - I Did Not Understand; Is There a Tomorrow? (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Jerusalem: Holy City (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Jewish-Christian Dialogue; The Jews in the Changing South (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Leaders and Leadership; Man and His Natural Heritage (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Method or Madness; Lecture on Parables (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Canon of Old Testament Lectures (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Lectures, Speeches Book Reviews, and Student Papers
    - Prophets and Philosophers - The Scandal of Prophecy (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Prayers (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - The Reestablishment of Worship; Religion and Society (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Remarks; Response (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Sermons (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Speech to 'Senate' - Shamus Club (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - A Shulkhan Arukh for Reform Judmaism (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - The Situation in the Middle East; Some Variations on the Theme (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Talks on Tenure (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - The Unconstrained God (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Book Reviews: A - H (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Book Reviews: I - Z (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Student Paper: Analytical Approach... - A Pluralistic Interpretation... (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Student Paper: Purpose of the Priestly Code - Religious Aspect of Philosophy (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Student Paper: A Short Study... (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Student Paper: Some Thomistic Principles of Beauty (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Notes
  - Academy for Jewish Studies, University Without Walls (1974) - Miscellaneous Notes (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Sermon "Alternatives Without a Choice" (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Lecture on "The Bible and Its Background" (Oct. Nov. 1950) (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Essenes (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Exegetical (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Form Criticism of Rabbinic Literature (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Moshe Greenberg's "Theology and History in the Book of Ezekial" (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Hasmonean Period - Pharasees, Sadducees, Sectaries (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Intermarriage, Jewish Community, etc. (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Intermarriage for Central Conference of American Rabbis Year Book (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Jewish History - Modern (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Lecture Outline on "The Jewish Idea of God" (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Jewish Life - Contemporary (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Jews-German Christians (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - "Judaism" article in Encyclopedia Britannica (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - "annus Ualatae" Article (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Mysticism (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Nature of Jewish Theology (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - For Silherman/Mead book Our Tradition (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Prayer (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Prophets and Philosophers: The Scandal of Prophecy (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Queen of Sheba (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Queen of Sheba (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Qumran (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Qumran (IQHiii [Plate 37]) (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Qumran (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Qumran (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Qumran (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Qumran (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Sermon Notes, etc. (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Sermon notes, etc. (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Speech given at Central Conference of American Rabbis Convention, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Suffering Servant, Isaiah 53 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Sukkot Festival, Hebrew Union College (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Toward a Rhetoric of Midrash - Carleton College (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - University of Chicago Religion Program (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Wellhausen and Judaism (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Worship (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 21, Folder 20)
- University Career
  - Teaching Responsibilities and Class Materials (Box 22)
    - Article Photocopies, etc. (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Article Photocopies, etc. (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Article Photocopies, etc. (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Article Photocopies, etc. (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Article Photocopies, etc. (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Article Photocopies, etc. (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Religion 101 (Introduction to Religion) - Syllabi (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Religion 101 (Introduction to Religion) - Syllabi (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Religion 101 (Introduction to Religion) - Syllabi (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Religion 101 (Introduction to Religion) - Syllabi (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Religion 101 (Introduction to Religion) - Lecture Notes (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Religion 101 (Introduction to Religion) - Lecture Notes (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Religion 101 (Introduction to Religion) - Reserve Lists, Exams, etc. (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Religion 105 (Introduction to Western Religion) - Syllabi (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Religion 105 (Introduction to Western Religion) - Exams, Class Tests (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Religion 105 (Introduction to Western Religion) -Reserve Lists, Book Orders (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Humanities 150-151 - Syllabi, Lecture Outlines, etc. (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Religion 221 (American Jewish Community) -Syllabi, Bibliographies, etc. (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Religion 228 (American Jewish Community) - Class Rosters, Book Orders, etc. (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Religion 228 (American Jewish Community) - Exams (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Religion 289b (Jewish Mysticism) - Syllabi, Reserve Lists (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Religion 301 (Hebrew Prophets) (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Class Materials (Box 22)
    - Religion 321/121 (History of Jewish People) - Syllabi, Exams (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Religion 121/321 (History of Jewish People) - Class Lists, Reserve Lists, etc. (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Religion 321/121 (History of Jewish People) - Lecture Notes (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Religion 321/121 (History of Jewish People) - Lecture Notes (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Religion 322 (Jewish Literature) - Syllabi, Reserve Lists, Exams (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Religion 322 (Jewish Literature) - Lecture Notes (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Religion 322 (Jewish Literature) - Lecture Notes (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Religion 322 (Jewish Literature) - Lecture Notes (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Religion 322 (Jewish Literature) - Lecture Notes (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Divinity 325 (Syriac) - Class Rosters, etc. (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Divinity 325 (Syriac) - Printed Tests (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Divinity 325 (Syriac) - Student Papers, Exams (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Divinity 325 (Syriac) - Lecture Notes, etc. (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Religion 504 (Psalms) - Class Rosters, Exams (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Religion 504/304 (Psalms) - Lecture Notes (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Religion 504/304 (Psalms) - Lecture Notes (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Religion 504/304 (Psalms) - Lecture Notes (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Divinity 504/304 (Psalms) - Lecture Notes, Miscellaneous (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Class Materials and Teaching Responsibilities (Box 24)
    - Religion 517/31G (Judaism in New Testament Period) Syllabi, Bibliographies, etc. (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Religion 517/316 (Judaism in New Testament Period) Exams (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Emory University - Contemporary Judaism (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Carleton College - Modern Judaism (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Carleton College - Modern Judaism, Chairperson (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Roll Books, Assorted Classes (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Dissertation Abstracts, A-Sm (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Dissertation Abstracts, S-W (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Dissertation Proposals, A-Cra (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Dissertation Proposals, Cre-D (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Dissertation Proposals, F-H (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Dissertation Proposals, I-J (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Dissertation Proposals, K-L (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Dissertation Proposals, Mc-M (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Dissertation Proposals, N-O (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Dissertation Proposals, Raitt (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Dissertation Proposals, Re-S (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Dissertation Proposals, T-Wi (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Dissertation Proposals, Ur-? (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Qualifying Exams - Biblical Theology (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Qualifying Exams - Church History (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Teaching Responsibi1ities (Box 25)
    - Qualifying Exams - Greek (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Qualifying Exams - Hebrew (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Qualifying Exams - Hebrew (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Qualifying Exams - History of Religion (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Qualifying Exams - Judaism (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Qualifying Exams - New Testament (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Qualifying Exams - Old Testament (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Qualifying Exams - Theology (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Sabbatical, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Sabbatical, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Sabbatical, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Student Papers, B (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Student Papers, D-H (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Student Papers, M-N (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Student Papers, 0-Sen (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Student Papers Sm-U (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Student Files (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Notes Re: Student Schedules (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Talmud Materials (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - University of Chicago (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Administrative Responsibilities (Box 26)
    - Afro-American Studies Program (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - American Association of Univ. Profs. (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Booksellers (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Chancellor, Miscellaneous Memoranda, etc. (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Commencement (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Deptartment of Religion Studies - Personnel, etc. (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Deptartment of Religion Studies - Reports, etc. (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Divinity School - Dean's Search Committee, Memoranda, etc. (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Divinity School - Dean's Search Committee Minutes (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Divinity School - Enrollment (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Divinity School - Faculty Colloquium (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Divinity School - Faculty Meeting Minutes, etc. (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Divinity School - Memoranda, etc. (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Divinity School - Personnel (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Divinity School - Reports, etc. (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Divinity School - Rules & Regulations (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Divinity School - VDS/Black Relations (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Divinity School - Miscellaneous (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Educational Policy Committee - Course Changes (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Educational Policy Committee - Meeting Minutes (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Educational Policy Committee - Memoranda (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Educational Policy Committee - Memoranda (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Educational Policy Committee - Memoranda (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Educational Policy Committee - Proposals (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Educational Policy Committee - Proposals (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Educational Policy Committee - Reports (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - Ethel Mae Wilson Fund (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - Faculty Committee on Tenure - Drafts, Notes, etc (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Administrative Responsibilities (Box 27)
    - Faculty Committee on Tenure - Drafts, Notes, etc (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Faculty Committee on Tenure - Drafts, Notes, etc (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Faculty Committee on Tenure - Drafts, Notes, etc (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Faculty Committee on Tenure - Drafts, Notes, etc. (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Faculty Committee on Tenure - Drafts, Notes, etc. (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Faculty Committee on Tenure - Drafts, Notes, etc. (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Faculty Committee on Tenure - Memoranda (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Faculty Committee on Tenure - Memoranda (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Faculty Committee on Tenure - Memoranda (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Faculty Committee on Tenure - Published Materials (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Faculty Committee on Tenure - Published Materials (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Faculty Committee on Tenure - Published Materials (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Faculty Committee on Tenure - Published Materials (Box 27, Folder 13)
      Book: Faculty Tenure. Commission on Academic Tenure
  - Administrative Responsibilities (Box 28)
    Book: The Tenure Debate. Barduell L. Smith & Associates
    - Faculty Committee on Tenure - Reports (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Faculty Committee on Tenure - Reports (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Faculty Committee on Tenure - Reports (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Faculty Committee on Tenure - Reports (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Faculty Committee on Tenure - Reports (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Faculty Committee on Tenure - Miscellaneous (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Faculty Council - Reports (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Faculty Senate, Committee on Agenda Development & Long Range Planning - Memoranda (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Faculty Senate, Committee on Agenda Development & Long Range Planning - Miscellaneous (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Financial (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Graduate Department of Religion - Enrollment (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Graduate Department of Religion - Faculty Meeting Minutes & Agenda (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Graduate Department of Religion - Memoranda (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Graduate Department of Religion - Ph.D. Theses in Progress (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Graduate Department of Religion - Programs (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Graduate Department of Religion - Qualifying Exams Samples (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Graduate Department of Religion - Qualifying Exam Schedules (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Graduate Department of Religion - Rules & Regulations; Tribal Lore (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Graduate Department of Religion - Rules & Regulations, Torah, etc. (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Graduate Faculty Council - Course Changes, etc. (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Graduate Faculty Council - Course Changes, etc. (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Administrative Responsibi1ities (Box 29)
    - Graduate Faculty Council - Course Changes, etc. (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Graduate Faculty Council - Financial Aid (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Graduate Faculty Council - Library (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Graduate Faculty Council - Meeting Agendas (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Graduate Faculty Council - Meeting Agendas (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Graduate Faculty Council - Meeting Minutes (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Graduate Faculty Council - Meeting Agendas (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Graduate Faculty Council - Memoranda (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Graduate Faculty Council - Memoranda (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Graduate Faculty Council - Memoranda (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Graduate Faculty Council - Minutes (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Graduate Faculty Council - Minutes (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Graduate Faculty Council - Minutes (Box 29, Folder 13)